{
    "subject": "resource/Miles_Davis",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Miles Davis",
    "human_readable": "The label of Miles Davis is 'Miles Davis'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9690577983856201,
            "question": "Is 'Miles Davis' a label or a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9401264190673828,
            "question": "Who is Miles Davis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9238530397415161,
            "question": "What is significant about the label 'Miles Davis'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9232898354530334,
            "question": "Why is it important to know that Miles Davis's label is 'Miles Davis'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8972514271736145,
            "question": "What is the name of Miles Davis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8501297831535339,
            "question": "What makes the label 'Miles Davis' unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8011118769645691,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Miles Davis besides his label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7559449076652527,
            "question": "How would you describe Miles Davis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7344971299171448,
            "question": "What type of work might be associated with the name Miles Davis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7143234610557556,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Miles Davis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Miles Davis is 'Miles Davis'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9296_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work might be associated with the name Miles Davis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9296_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Miles Davis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9296_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Miles Davis besides his label?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9296_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9296_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents discuss Miles Davis' career and musical legacy but do not mention the label he was associated with. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Miles Davis as a musician, including his career and records. However, they do not contain any information to support the claim that \"The label of Miles Davis is 'Miles Davis'\". In this context, it seems more appropriate to refer to him by his name rather than a label."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context, there isn't any specific information that confirms or denies that \"The label of Miles Davis is 'Miles Davis'.\" This phrase seems to be ambiguous and not clearly related to the content in the documents. The documents mainly talk about his influence as a jazz musician, the albums he recorded, his career timeline, and collaborations with other musicians but do not provide any specific information regarding a label called \"Miles Davis.\"\n\nTherefore, the answer would be:\n```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the lack of direct evidence in the documents to support or refute the statement."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple texts state Miles Davis was signed to labels like Columbia Records and Warner Brothers.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Miles Davis was a musician, not a label. The context mentions labels such as Columbia Records and Warner Brothers where Miles Davis recorded his albums, but the name \"Miles Davis\" refers to the artist himself, not a record label.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}